https://boskalis.com/privacy-statement.html

Close menu
Search
HomeAbout usCompany profileOrganizational structureStrategyResearch and developmentBuilding with NatureHistorySponsorshipLinksCompany profileFleet and equipmentDredgersTrailing suction hopper dredgersCutter suction dredgersBackhoe dredgersFloating grab cranesVarious dredging vessels and equipmentDredgersOffshore vesselsHeavy transport vesselsCable-laying / multipurpose vesselsFallpipe vesselsDiving support vesselsOceangoing and anchor handling tugsHeavy lift vesselsVarious offshore vessels and equipmentOffshore vesselsFleet investmentsFleet and equipmentProjectsAbout usBoskalis at a glance - who we are, what we do and what sets us apart.About usHighlights HY2020 Revenue: EUR 1.3 billion EBITDA: EUR 204 million Operating result: EUR 72 million Net operating profit: EUR 48 million Extraordinary charges: EUR 148 million Order book: EUR 4.7 billion Positive net cash position of EUR 190 million Read the full reportActivitiesDredging & Inland InfraConstruction and maintenance of portsCoastal defense and riverbank protectionLand reclamationEngineeringSpecialist servicesDredging & Inland InfraOffshore energyTransportOil and gas installationOffshore wind farm installationSubsea IRM & SURFDecommissioningOffshore support servicesIntegrated offshore solutionsOffshore energyTowageSalvageActivitiesOur activities include dredging, offshore contracting and marine services, including heavy marine transport, towage and salvage.ActivitiesNo Injuries, No AccidentsSafety has been a priority within the Boskalis organization for years. For continuous improvement of our safety culture and to reach our goal of an incident-free working environment, we have the NINA safety program in place.Read moreMarketsPortsPort development and maintenancePort servicesPortsOffshore energyOil and gas exploration - offshore drilling rigsOil and gas production - shallow waterOil and gas production - deep waterOil and gas refining and processingRenewable energyOffshore energyInfraLand reclamationCoastal protectionInland ports and waterwaysEnvironmental servicesRoads and railwaysTunnels and bridgesInfraMarketsBoskalis operates in the ports, offshore energy and infrastructure markets. These markets anticipate structural growth over the longer term as a result of several key global trends.MarketsBOKA Vanguard loaded Carnival VistaSemi-submersible heavy lift vessel BOKA Vanguard loaded and transported cruise ship Carnival Vista for a unique dry-docking operation.
IRKey figuresOutlookFinancial publicationsCorporate governanceBoard of ManagementSupervisory BoardRisk managementStrategic and market risksOperational risksFinancial risksOther risksInternal risk management and control systemsRisks regarding financial reportingEvaluation of risk management and internal control systemsRisk managementCorporate governance principlesGeneral Meeting of ShareholdersAuditorCorporate governanceFinancial calendarShare informationShare chartsShareholdersShare buybackDividendShare informationAnalyst coverage & EstimatesIR policyInvestor relations contactInvestor relationsWe strive to inform our stakeholders as completely as possible and to provide insight into the strategic direction and performance of the company.IRHighlights HY2020 Revenue: EUR 1.3 billion EBITDA: EUR 204 million Operating result: EUR 72 million Net operating profit: EUR 48 million Extraordinary charges: EUR 148 million Order book: EUR 4.7 billion Positive net cash position of EUR 190 million Read the full reportSustainabilityStrategy and prioritiesMateriality assessmentWorking towards global goalsInnovation and partnershipsStrategy and prioritiesCreating shared valueEnergy transitionClimate change adaptationSalvage and Marine Ecosystem ProtectionCreating shared valueFocus areasClimate changeBiodiversity and ecosystemsLocal community and developmentEmployee and talent developmentSafetyFocus areasResponsible businessReportsCasesCreating sustainable horizonsRead more about our approach to manage social and environmental impacts.SustainabilitySustainability at BoskalisWe create and protect welfare and advance the energy transition.More about our strategyCareersCareersLooking to create new horizons?Our corporate website gives an impression of what Boskalis does. If you are interested in finding out more about what it is like to work for us, take a look at our dedicated Careers website.CareersLooking to create new horizons?We have 9,600 experts working with us around the globe.
Interested in joining us? Have a look at our current vacancies and apply online.
Read more
Download center
Press
Contact
Nederlands
Nederlands
Download center
Press
Contact
Boskalis is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of the information entrusted to us. That means that Boskalis aims to safeguard the protection and correct use of your personally identifiable information (referred to as ‘personal information’). This Privacy Statement applies to the websites of Boskalis. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform visitors of the websites and users of services and information provided by Boskalis about how Boskalis handles personal information. This Privacy Statement describes how we collect, use, share and protect personal information. It is available in various languages.
Download and read
Online privacy statement
Download
English
(77 KB)
Deutsch
(80 KB)
Nederlands
(77 KB)
Back to top
Cookies
To ensure you have the best experience on our website, we use cookies. Click ‘Yes, I agree’ to accept cookies. View our cookie policy to learn more.
Yes, I agree
No, I don't agree
